afterlife.co 2018-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Afterlife

1\. In General

This policy is written in accordance with the laws and regulations of the Province of Quebec.

This Privacy Policy informs users of how their information is collected, used or communicated. Except when otherwise stated on afterlife.co, the site is open to all users. Therefore, by using this website, by becoming a member or by subscribing to the different services offered, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

We strongly suggest you read this Privacy Policy carefully before using our website or submitting any personal information.

afterlife.co reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Privacy Policy by updating this web page, without prior notice.

The policies described on this page are only valid for afterlife.co and do not apply to any of the sites afterlife.co is linked to.

afterlife.co does not offer any guarantee and is not responsible for any of the other websites to which a user might be granted access through afterlife.co.

2\. Collecting information

Names, addresses, postal codes, marital statuses, dates of birth, emails, are all personal information that users voluntarily choose to submit when subscribing. The users agree that the submitted and collected information is used to respond to their expectation towards afterlife.co. 

Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information

We use cookies and various other technologies to collect information from your computer. Each time you visit our website, information is automatically collected from your browser. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, language as well as access times and is used by afterlife.co to know the number of people having access to afterlife.co. 

Our website might share some of this information with third parties but does not provide any personal information to these parties. Users may change the settings of their browsers to refuse or destroy these cookies.

3\. Use of collected information

Personal information collected is never shared with third parties for the purpose of publicity or marketing uses.

Only the general information submitted by users through their profile on afterlife.co is published online.

Users may, in any time, withdraw the information they submitted or correct them online or by communicating with afterlife.co.

In some situations, afterlife.co may have to share information with government agencies and other corporations. This is notably the case:

1\. When it is allowed or required by law;

2\. To respond to an emergency situation where someone's life, well-being or security is at stake;

3\. To hold an internal investigation into a possible infringement to a Canadian law; 

4\. When the information is already accessible to the public.

4\. Security

The recognizable personal information is safeguarded by being stocked and encrypted during its transmission. Only an authorized employee of afterlife.co can have access to this information.

afterlife.co is equipped with a system to protect the transmitted information. However, afterlife.co is not to be held responsible for the transmission of any type of computer virus in any shape or form. Surfing or downloading information on the website is done at the users' own risks.

Users are responsible not to disclose confidential information in their profile and in the messages they send to other users via afterlife.co. 

5\. Other policies

This policy is governed, interpreted and supervised by the laws applicable in the Province of Quebec and all litigious matters that may arise from it are to be decided by the judiciary of Quebec City, Province of Quebec.

For any questions pertaining to this Privacy Policy or if you like to request information on afterlife.co is inner workings or its Terms and Conditions Agreement, please contact afterlife.co costumer service.
